[
    {
        "question": "Who is the main protagonist of Dragon Ball?",
        "choices" : ["Vegeta", "Son Goku", "Piccolo", "Yamchu"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Goku's signature attack?",
        "choices": ["Kamehameha", "Kaio-ken", "Masenko", "Ki Blast"],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Goku's brother?",
        "choices": ["Vegeta", "Bardock", "Nappa", "Radditz"],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What race does Goku belong to?",
        "choices": ["Human", "Saiyan", "Namekian", "Majin"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Who kills Frieza on Namek?",
        "choices": ["Piccolo", "Son Gohan", "Son Goku", "Vegeta"],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Krillin and Son Goku's master?",
        "choices": ["Jackie Chun", "Muten Roshi", "Kami", "King Kai"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Who becomes the guardian of Earth after Kami?",
        "choices": ["King Kai", "Son Gohan", "Dende", "Piccolo"],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Dragon Balls are there in total?",
        "choices": ["5", "7", "9", "3"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Son Goku's Saiyan name?",
        "choices": ["Kakarot", "Bardock", "Broly", "Nappa"],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Son Goku's wife?",
        "choices": ["Bulma", "Chi-Chi", "Videl", "Launch"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Who trained Son Gohan as a child in the wilderness?",
        "choices": ["Piccolo", "Goku", "Master Roshi", "Krillin"],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Who created the Androids?",
        "choices": ["Frieza", "Dr. Gero", "Bulma", "King Kai"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character can regenerate his body parts?",
        "choices": ["Piccolo", "Goku", "Vegeta", "Krillin"],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the first character to ever perform a Kamehameha?",
        "choices": ["Goku", "Krillin", "Muten Roshi", "Gohan"],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Who did Future Trunks warn the Z Fighters about?",
        "choices": ["Frieza", "Androids", "Broly", "King Cold"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Who does Son Goku defeat in the final round of the 21st World Martial Arts Tournament?",
        "choices": ["Krillin", "Jackie Chun", "Tien", "Yamcha"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the leader of the Red Ribbon Army?",
        "choices": ["Commander Red", "General Blue", "Mercenary Tao", "Colonel Violet"],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What animal is Muten Roshi's pet companion?",
        "choices": ["Tiger", "Pig", "Turtle", "Dog"],
        "answer": 2
    }
]